妈
Mom.
妈妈可是个美女啊
Mom is a babe.
你也是猎人吗
Are you a hunter?
- 嗨 温彻斯特家的小子 - 你怎么来这儿了 下士
- Hey, winchester! son of a bitch! - How you doin', corporal?
你好 D先生
Hey, Mr.D.
老爸？
Dad?
这听起来有一点疯狂
This is gonna sound a little crazy.
- 玛丽是我的妈妈 - 什么
- Mary is my mother. - Excuse me?
我是你的孙子
And I am your grandson.
我是玛丽和约翰 温彻斯特的儿子
My parents are mary and John winchester.
- 我不知道你在说啥 - 玛丽是被黄眼魔鬼杀掉的
- I don't know. - Mary gets killed by a yellow-eyed demon.
你不想得到那些人的灵魂
You don't want those people's souls.
- 不 我只是想得到他们的孩子 - 为什么选他们
- No, i just want their children. - Why any of them?
我会盯着他们的婴儿床
I'm gonna stand over their crib,
而且我会把我的血灌进他们的嘴巴里
and I'm gonna bleed into their mouths.
那么 你一直在用那个奇怪的预知未来的能力
So, you've been using your freaky e.s.p. stuff?
没有 你确定？
No. sure about that?
看吧 你不想我在这条路上走下去
Look, you didn't want me to go down that road,
所以我就不会走这条路
So I didn't go down that road.
好的 我们就保持这这样子吧
Well, let's keep it that way.
我们知道是亚撒色对你弟弟做了什么
We know what azazel did to your brother.
但我们不知道为什么
What we don't know is why.
迪恩 你弟弟走上了一条不归路
Your brother is heading down a dangerous road, Dean, so stop it…
你要阻止他
so stop it…
要不然我们就动手了
Or we will.
莉莉丝在哪
Where's lilith?
见鬼去吧
Kiss my ass.
如果我是你我就会万事小心一点
I'd watch myself if I were you.
为啥
Why? huh?
因为你是萨姆 温彻斯特 大英雄先生
Because you're sam winchester, mr. big hero?
然而这就是你 和一些魔鬼鬼混
And yet here you are, slutting around with some demon.
- 「真正的英雄」 - 闭嘴
- Real hero. - Shut your mouth.
跟我说说没有你哥哥的日子
Tell me about those months without your brother…
还有所有关于你还有这个婊子在暗处里进行的勾当
About all the things you and this demon bitch do in the dark.
怎样 跟我说说吧 大英雄
Huh? tell me, hero.
[邪恶力量 第4季第4集]
感觉怎样
How'd it feel?
很不错 头不痛了 一点都不痛了吗
Good. no more headaches. none?
很好
That is good.
我在你身边 没事的
I got you. it's all right.
那么…
So…
萨姆 你有什么事情要告诉我
Anything you want to tell me, sam?
迪恩 等等 好吗 让我
Dean, hold on, okay? just let me.
你想说让我来解释是吗
you gonna say, "let me explain"?
你想解释这档子事吗
You're gonna explain this?
不如这样
How about this?
为什么不从她是谁
Why don't you start with who she is.
和这里他妈的发生了什么事开始说起
and what the hell is she doing here?
看到你真高兴啊 迪恩
It's good to see you again, Dean.
露比？
Ruby?
是露比？
Is that ruby?
不要
Don't!
露比 住手
Ruby, stop it.
你不是很听这个小贱人的话吗
Well, aren't you an obedient little bitch?
露比
Ruby.
露比 他很受伤
Ruby…he's hurt.
快
Go.
你们要去哪里
Where the hell do you think you're going?
除非你想去其他地方先
The e.r…unless you want to go another round first.
迪恩
Dean.
Dean!
迪恩 你在干什么
Dean, what are you doing?
干嘛 你要走了吗
What, Are you… are you leaving?
你不需要我了 你跟露比去解决恶魔就好啦
You don't need me. you and ruby go fight demons.
等一下 迪恩 别这样
Hold on. Dean, come on, man.
你满意了吧
You satisfied?
我猜没有
I guess not.
你知不知道你已经偏离我们原来的生活有多远了
Do you even know how far off the reservation you've gone?
离正常有多远 还是里正常人有多远
How far from normal? from human?
我只是在驱魔
I'm just exorcising demons.
用你的意志
With your mind!
你还能做什么
What else can you do?
我可以把他们送回地狱
I can send them back to hell.
只是和魔鬼联手 就这样
It only works with demons, and that's it.
你还能做什么 我已经告诉你了
What else can you do?! I told you!
我有什么理由去相信你
And I have every reason in the world to believe that.
看吧 我早就该说些什么了
Look, i should have said something.
迪恩 我很对不起
I'm sorry, Dean. I am.
可是试着看看事情的另一面 另一面？
But try to see the other side here. the other side?!
我在将魔鬼从无辜的人们的身体里驱逐出去 用这把刀
I'm pulling demons out of innocent people. use the knife!
这把到把无辜的人也杀掉了
The knife kills the victim!
现在我这么做 大多数人都能活下来
What I do, most of them survive!
看看
Look,
我在这五个月里救活的人比
I've saved more people in the last five months.
我们过去一年里救的人都多
than we save in a year.
那露比要你去想些什么
That what ruby wants you to think?
她用什么方法
Kind of like the way she tricked you.
骗你去使用你的力量
into using your powers?
兄弟 滑坡效应
Slippery slope, brother.
尽管看看吧
Just wait and see.
因为越来越黑暗了
Because it's gonna get darker and darker,
上帝知道什么时候要结束
and god knows where it ends.
我不会让这走得太远了
I'm not gonna let it go too far.
萨姆 这已经走得很远了
It's already gone too far, sam.
如果我不认识你
If I didn't know you…
我会想要去找到你
…i would want to hunt you.
其他的猎人也一样
And so would other hunters.
你死过一次了
You were gone.
我还在
I was here.
我要继续在没有你的陪伴下作战
I had to keep on fighting without you.
而且我现在做的事
And what I'm doing…
行得通
It works.
那么跟我说说
Well, tell me.
如果这是这么棒的话
If it's so terrific…
那么为什么你当初要骗我
Then why'd you lie about it to me?
为什么天使说告诉我要去阻止你
Why did an angel tell me to stop you?
什么
What?
卡西迪奥说我不来阻止你 他就会亲自动手了
Cas said that if I don't stop you, he will.
懂了吧
See, what that means,
萨姆 这意味着上帝不愿意让你做这事
Sam, that means that god doesn't want you doing this.
那么你还要跟我争
So, are you just gonna stand there and.
说这一切都是好的吗
and tell me that everything is all good?
喂？
Hello?
你好 特拉维斯
Hey, travis. yeah, hey.
嗯 听到你的声音真好 是的
Uh…it's good to hear your voice, too, yeah.
嗯 等等 现在我有点事儿
Um, look, it's not a really good time right now.
好 行
Yeah, okay.
嗯 好吧 给我具体的地址 还有 迦太基 密苏里
Uh, well, just give me the details, and, uh carthage, missouri.
找杰克·蒙哥马利
Looking for jack montgomery.
杰克 你觉得很难下咽
Jack, are you stoned?
什么 很好吃 我饿得要命
What? it's good. I'm starving.
还有甜品吗
Is…is there dessert?
刚刚弄好
It just so happens.
嘿 宝贝儿
Hey, babe?
嗯 你还吃剩下的牛排吗
Hmm? are you gonna finish your steak?
你在开玩笑吧 你都吃完两份了
You're kidding, right? you've had two already.
我也不清楚 我只是还饿
I don't know. I'm just…hungry.
或许你肚子里长了绦虫
Or you have tapeworm.
拜托
Please.
我感觉挺好的
I never felt better.
真不敢相信 老妈 是个猎人
I can't believe it. mom a hunter?
如果不是我亲眼看到我也不会相信的
I wouldn't have believed it, either, if I hadn't seen it myself.
那女人厉害着呢
That woman could kick some ass.
我是说 她差点把我放倒
I mean, she almost took me down.
她看起来怎么样
How'd she look?
我的意思是 她快乐吗
I mean…was she happy?
当然 她好极了
Yeah, she was awesome.
既可爱又聪明
Funny and smart.
前途无限
So hopeful.
老爸也是
Dad, too.
当然 直到
Until, of course…
怎么了
What?
没什么
Nothing.
只是 现在我们发现我们父母 以及外祖父母全都是猎人
It's just our parents, and now we find out our grandparents, too?
而我们整个家族都被杀了 但是为什么
Our whole family murdered, and for what?
那个黄眼要到我的婴儿房里还滴血到我嘴里
So yellow eyes could get in my nursery and bleed in my mouth?
萨姆 我从没说过任何关于恶魔之血的事
Sam, i never said anything about demon blood.
你早就知道了？
You knew about that?
是的 已经一年了
Yeah, for about a year.
整整一年了
A whole year.
我知道应该告诉你的 我很抱歉
I should have told you. I'm sorry.
你最近说了很多次这样的话了 萨姆
You've been saying that a lot lately, sam.
但不管怎样
But whatever.
你不想告诉我的话 你完全不必说
You don't want to tell me, you don't have to.
- 那没关系 - 迪恩
- It's fine. - Dean.
随你怎么想
Whatever.
嘿 宝贝儿 什么时候开饭
Hey, babe, when's dinner?
45分钟之后
45 minutes.
我饿了
I'm starving!
杰克 一顿美味的家常饭不同于速食食品和外卖 需要等待
Jack, a delicious, unmicrowaved, non-takeout, homemade meal is coming.
你确定就是这家伙
Are you sure that's him?
城里就一个杰克·蒙哥马利
Only jack montgomery in town.
那我们要…
And we're looking for…?
特拉维斯只是说留意任何怪异之处
Travis said to keep an eye out for anything weird.
怪异
Weird?
是的
Yeah.
好吧 怪异和不怪异的我都见过
All right, well, yeah, I've seen big weird, little weird,
甚至是怪异到癫狂的
Weird with crazy on top.
但这家伙 就我看 得了 这家伙正常得要死
But this guy? I mean, come on, this guy's boring.
我也不清楚 迪恩 特拉维斯说得煞有其事的
I don't know, Dean. travis seemed pretty sure.
亲爱的
Honey.
我想说这真是够怪异的
I'd say that qualifies as weird.
特拉维斯
Travis.
看吧 萨姆 我早就告诉你要把啤酒藏起来
See, sam. told you we should have hid the beer.
小坏蛋们 快过来
Smartass. get over here!
噢 见到你真高兴
Ohh, good to see you.
- 见到你也是 - 见到你真高兴
- You too. - good to see you.
见到你也是 特拉维斯
You too, travis.
小子 你长高了
Man, you got tall, kid.
多长时间没见过了
How long has it been?
哦 天啊 快十年了
Oh, got to be 10 years.
你仍然是 噢 那怎么说来着？奥数参赛者？
You still a… Oh, what was it? a mathlete?
早不是了
No.
是 当然是
Yep, sure is.
都这么多年了 孩子们
Been too long, boys.
我是说 看看你们 都长大成人了
I mean, look at you, grown men.
约翰一定为你们而感到骄傲
John would have been damn proud of you…
看到你们如此同心协力
Sticking together like this.
是啊 是啊 我们很亲密无间的
Yeah. yeah, we're as thick as thieves.
没什么会比家庭更重要
Nothing more important than family.
对不起 我迟到了点
Sorry I'm late for the dance.
谢谢你们能出面帮我这个老头子
Thanks for helping out an old man.
况且我还有点少胳膊少腿儿的
I'm a little, uh, shorthanded.
那么 你们找到蒙哥马利了
So, you track down montgomery?
是的 我们在他家找到他的 - 然后呢
- Yeah, we found him at his home. - and?
嗯 我们看到他那恶心的零食
Well, he had a hell of a case of the munchies,
他在那里生吃东西
Topped off with a burger that he forgot to cook.
- 那就对了 就是他了 - 他是什么东西
- That's him, all right. - What's him?
小伙子们 我们找到了一个洛格鲁
Boys, we got a rougarou on our hands.
洛格鲁（一种法国流传的食肉怪）
A rougarou?
这是合成词 这听起来是合成的
Is that made up? that sounds made up.
他们的意思是 恶心的啃食者 腐朽的牙齿 虫状的皮肤便于他们啃食
They're mean, nasty little suckers… rotted teeth, wormy skin, the works.
那么 这已经不算是人了
Well, that ain't this guy.
我意思是 他只是套了一副皮囊
I mean, he was wearing a cellphone on his belt.
他很快会变得丑陋起来
He'll turn ugly soon enough.
从本质说 他们始变于人类
They start out human, for all intents and purposes.
那么 是有什么东西会导致他们变形
So, what, they go through some kind of metamorphosis?
对 就像蛆变成一只苍蝇那样
Yep, like a maggot turning into a bull fly.
但最重要的是 他们总是很饥渴
But most of all, they're hungry.
怎么个饥渴法
Hungry for what?
起初 是对所有的东西 接着就会是人肉
At first, for everything, but then for long pig.
长猪
Long pig?
他的意思是活人
He means human flesh.
我就是那个意思
And that is my word of the day.
当他们再也无法抵御那种饥饿感
Hunger grows in till they can't fight it,
直到他们对着活生生的人一口咬下时 一切就开始了
Till they got to take themselves a big, juicy chomp, and then it happens.
开始什么
What happens?
他们会很快的完全转变
They transform completely and fast.
我想我需要创可贴
I think I need stitches.
我得出去
I got to go.
什么？
What?
我要离开这里
I got to get out of here.
你要去哪 杰克
Where are you going? jack?!
咬一口就全完了眼睛 牙齿 皮肤都要变异
One bite's all it takes yes, teeth, skin all turns.
也不会恢复回去的
No going back, either.
只要吃过一次人 他们就永远是怪物了
They feed once, they're a monster forever.
杰克就快变成这样了
And our man jack's headed there on a bullet train.
如果他是人类 那你是怎么找到这家伙的？
Well, how'd you find this guy if he's a walking, talking human?
他们家很不幸
Let's just say it runs in his family.
你个意思是…
You mean, uh…
早在78年我就杀了他爸爸
Killed his daddy back in '78.
在我搞定他之前那杂种已经毁了8具尸体了
Son of a bitch mangled eight bodies before I put him down.
这家伙曾是个牙医 有辆卡迪拉克 一个好太太
Guy used to be a dentist dillac, trophy wife.
我还知道点 他太太怀孕了
Little did I know, pregnant trophy wife.
她把孩子养大了
She put the boy up for adoption.
当我发现时他早就销声匿迹了
By the time I found out, he was long gone, lost in the system.
你的意思是你没找到那家伙？
You mean to tell me you couldn't find someone?
我不知道我是不是想找他
I'm not sure I wanted to.
要我去猎杀可怜的孩子们
The idea of hunting down some poor kid…
我狠不下这个心
I don't think I'd have had the heart.
我要等下去 直到确定我找对了人
No. wanted to wait, make damn sure I had the right man.
很明显 我找到了
Apparently, i do.
再来一杯 谢谢
One more, please.
我能再来点花生吗？
Can I get some more peanuts?
想喝点什么？
Come on. what are you drinking?
我请客
It's my treat.
不了 谢谢
No, thank you.
表这样撒 陪我喝一杯嘛
Oh, don't be like that. have a drink with me.
我在等人
I'm waiting for someone.
- 好吧 那他人呢？-喂 饭桶
- Okay, well, where is he? - Hey, douche bag.
她不想跟你说话
She doesn't want to talk to you.
什么？你再说一遍？
I'm sorry. I didn't hear you.
我说
I said…
她不想跟你说话 你个傻逼胖子
She doesn't want to talk to you, you fat…sweaty…dick.
离她远点 立刻
Now, leave her alone.
你 当真要这么干？
You, uh, seriously want to do this, guy?
没错 我是这么想的
You know, I really think I do.
那么 用火烧吗？
So, fire, huh?
唯一能干掉这些畜生的方法就是把它们烧成灰
The only way I found to kill these bastards deep-fry 'em.
那可真是…恐怖哦
Well, that's gonna be… horrible.
你就是这样对付杰克的爸爸的？
Is that what you did to jack's dad?
你们没浪费时间吧？
Not wasting any time, are you?
没人想浪费时间
None to waste.
那家伙要是暴走了我们就死无全尸了
The guy hulks out, we won't be finding bodies, just remains.
要是他没暴走呢？
What if he doesn't hulk out?
我做了点准备
I did a little homework.
我已经用洛格鲁检验了下诱饵
I've been checking out the lure on rougarous.
难道我30年的经验对你来说还不够？
What, my 30 years of experience not good enough for you?
什么？
What?
不 不是这个意思 我只是想准备好罢了
No. no, i-i just wanted to be prepared.
- 我是说 不是你不够 - 萨姆喜欢做调查 他就这样的
- I mean, not that you didn't. - Sam loves research. He does.
而且喜欢放在床垫下的润蓓旁边（人体润滑剂）
He keeps it under his mattress right next to his k-y.
有毛病 确实有毛病
It's a sickness. it is.
你说你检查过的东西当然没问题了 但是
Look, everything you said checked out, of course, but, uh,
我找到了些有关那些
I found a couple of interesting stories about.
带有洛格鲁基因之类东西的的人的趣闻
People who have this rougarou gene or whatever.
想想看 他们开始变异了 但不完全 对吧？
See, they start to turn, but they never take the final step. really?
再想想 要是他们从来不吃人肉 他们就不会完全变异
See, if they never eat human flesh, they don't fully transform.
- 那又怎样？不吃肉 保持人形？-基本是这样
- So, what? Go vegan, stay human? - Basically.
- 或者在这件事上 吃很多生肉 - 吃人肉 - 没错
- Or in this case, eat a lot of raw meat, just not… - Long pig. - Right.
你没瞎忙活 萨姆
Good on you for the due diligence, sam.
但那些都是童话
But those are fairy tales.
事实是 每个我见过或听说过的洛格鲁
Fact is, every rougarou I ever saw or heard of…
没有不吃人肉的
Took that bite.
好吧 但这也不意味着杰克也是这样的
Okay, well, that doesn't mean that jack will.
那么 我们该怎么办？
So, what do we do?
怀着希望坐等遇害者？
Sit and hope and wait for a body count?
不 我们跟他谈谈 解释下发生了什么
No, we talk to him, explain what's happening.
这么做他就能自救了
That way, he can fight it.
自救？
Fight it?
你在搞笑吗？
Are you kidding me?
你挨过饿吗？
You ever been really hungry?
我指的是被饿得死去活来的？
I mean, haven't-eaten-in-days hungry?
- 对 - 然后
- Yeah, yeah. - Right, then.
有人丢了一块肥美多汁的里脊肉给你 你会不吃？
Somebody slaps a big, juicy sirloin in front of you, you walking away?
对他而言 我们就是这块肉 肥肉
That's what we are to him now meat on legs.
我知道他是个正直的人 我很遗憾
I'm sorry. I'm sure he's a stand-up guy.
但吃人纯粹是他的本能
But it's pure, base instinct.
生物都要吃东西
Everything in nature's got to eat.
- 你觉得单凭人品他就能控制自己了？-我不知道
- You think he can stop himself 'cause he's nice? - I don't know.
但是不到迫不得已我们不能杀他
But we're not gonna kill him unless he does something to get killed for.
你弟弟怎么了？
What's up with your brother?
别问我
Don't get me started.
上帝啊 你吓死我了
God. you scared me.
对不起 我没想吓你
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to sneak up on you.
你怎么样了？
How are you feeling?
我很火大 杰克
I'm feeling pissed, jack.
昨天晚上我只能一个人开车去医院
I had to drive myself to the hospital last night.
我在医院待到两点
I was there until 2:00.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
- 发生什么了？-我不知道
- What happened? - I don't know.
我看到你流血了 我一阵眩晕 我只能出去
I saw your blood, and i-i…got dizzy, and I just had to get out.
你可以去打电话的 我给你留了无数条留言
Well, you could have called. I left you a dozen messages.
我知道 手机没电了 我没找到公共电话
I know. my phone died. I couldn't find a pay phone.
我 真是一团糟
I …it was a mess.
我真的…很抱歉
But I am…sorry.
我发誓不会再发生这种事了
And I promise it won't ever happen again.
绝对不会
Certainly…
尤其对你 一位绝美的妻子
Not to a wife as stunning as you.
最好别
Better not.
一个小小的伤口
I swear, you know. one little cut.
你以前没这样过啊
Blood's never bothered you before.
现在是了
Well…i've changed.
这不会困扰你的
This doesn't get you off the hook, you know.
不 不 想想钻石 想想超大号钻石
No, no. Think… think diamond. think kobe-sized.
你被什么上身了
What has gotten into you?
我不知道
I don't know.
杰克 慢点
Hey, jack. just slow down.
杰克
Jack.
杰克 我是说真的 停一下
Jack, i mean it. stop.
杰克
Jack. ow!
杰克 停手
Jack! stop!
停手 停手
Stop it! stop it!
你这混蛋
You son of bitch.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你到底怎么回事呀
What the hell is wrong with you?
我不知道
I don't know.
那么我们要去找那家伙聊聊
All right, so we're gonna go have a little chat with this guy, which,
你知道我不在行的
You know, i'm down.
只想确认下没有回旋的余地了吗
But I just want to make sure, if push comes, you're gonna shove.
你想说什么
Meaning?
我们可能要活活烧死他啊
Well, odds are we're gonna have to burn this guy alive.
他可是有名有姓又有妻室
This guy has a name and a wife.
是啊 而他老婆则有可能成为寡妇是吗
Yeah, who we're probably gonna make a widow, okay?
你听过特拉维斯说的了
I mean, you heard travis.
他会变异 他们总是会变异
He's gonna turn. they always turn.
也许他不会 也许他能战胜兽性
Well, maybe he won't. maybe he can fight it off.
也许他战胜不了 我言尽于此
And maybe he can't. that's all I'm saying.
好吧 我们只是去看看好吗
All right, we'll just have to see, then, okay?
我也是这意思 萨姆
This is what I mean, sam.
你确定没有融入私人感情在里面
You sure your emotions aren't getting in the way here?
你说什么
What are you talking about?
这个不错的家伙血液中却透着点邪恶
You know, nice dude, but he's got something evil inside.
在他的血液里 也许你可以联系到什么
Something in his blood. maybe you can relate.
停车
Stop the car.
怎么了
What?
停车否则我跳车
Stop the car or I will.
你想知道我为什么要骗你吗 迪恩
you want to know why I've been lying to you, Dean?
- 就因为这些个狗屁事 - 什么事
- Because of crap like this! - Like what?
你和我说话的方式 在你眼中我就像个怪物
The way you talk to me, the way you look at me like I'm a freak!
- 我没有 - 你知道吗或许更糟 就像个白痴
- I do not. - You know, or even worse, like I'm an idiot!
分不清孰是孰非
Like I don't know the difference between right and wrong!
怎么了
What?
你分得清吗 萨姆
Do you know the difference, sam?
就像深夜迷失在幽深小道上
I mean, you've been kind of strolling a dark road lately.
你根本就不知道我经历着什么 一无所知
You have no idea what I'm going through. none.
那就告诉我
Then enlighten me!
我血液中透着魔性 迪恩
I've got demon blood in me, Dean!
而这种魔性遍布着我的全身
This disease pumping through my veins,
去不掉也洗不掉
And I can't ever rip it out or scrub it clean!
我是全新一级的怪物
I'm a whole new level of freak!
而我尽力把这个诅咒
And I'm just trying to take this…this curse…
往好的一面发展
And make something good out of it.
因为我必须这么做
Because I have to.
让我们去和那家伙聊聊吧
Let's just go talk to the guy.
我是说杰克 好吗
I mean jack. okay?
杰克·蒙哥马利
Jack montgomery?
我是萨姆·温彻斯特 这是我哥 迪恩
I'm sam winchester. this is my brother, Dean.
我们想要和你聊聊
We need to talk.
关于什么
About?
有关你
About you.
有关你如何变异
About how you're changing.
你说什么
Excuse me?
你可能感觉到骨头在你皮下移位
You're probably feeling your bones move under your skin…
食欲到了顶峰
And your appetite's reaching, you know, hungry hungry hippo levels.
我说的对吗
How am I doing so far?
你们到底是谁
Who the hell are you guys?
我们是对某事略知一二的人
We're people who know a little something about something.
我们是来帮你的
We're people who can help.
请听我们说完
Please, just hear us out.
叫什么来着
A-a what?
洛格鲁
A rougarou.
听起来像捏造的 但相信我 这是真的
Sounds made-up, i know, but, believe me, it's not.
好吧 我注意到一些事情
All right, I've noticed certain things.
一些奇怪的事 但我只是 我不知道
I mean, some strange things, but I just I don't know.
我病了或是怎么了
I'm…I'm sick or something.
你父亲就是其中一只
Your father was one of these things.
你的亲生父亲 遗传了这基因给你
Your real father. he passed it on to you.
不可能
No.
你们清楚自己在说什么吗
Are you guys listening to yourselves?
听起来你们是 略过那句听起来你们疯了 是吗
You sound like you're… skip the whole "you guys sound crazy, " shall we?
你很渴望 杰克 会变得越来越渴望的
You're hungry, jack. you're only gonna get hungrier.
渴望什么
Hungrier for?
人肉
Long pig.
一些人肉汉堡制作已经在你脑海中闪现
You know, a little manburger helper may have crossed your mind already.
没有
No.
事情并非无法控制 杰克
It doesn't have to be like this, jack.
你可以战胜兽性 有人成功过
You can fight it off. others have.
我们不想骗你 这绝非易事
We're not gonna lie to you, though. it's not gonna be easy.
你会感觉自己是个酒鬼在威士忌中畅游
You're gonna feel like an alcoholic swimming around in whiskey.
- 但我要告诉你 你必须说不 否则 - 否则怎样
- But I'm telling you, you got to say no, or… - Or what?
只要你尝了一次 一发而不可收拾
You feed once, and it's all over.
然后我们必须得制止你
And then we'll have to stop you.
制止我
Stop me?
我父亲 有人制止了他吗
My dad did, Uh, somebody stop him?
是的
Yes.
马上给我滚出这里
Get off my property right now.
要再让我看见你们 我就会报警
I see you guys again, I'm calling the cops.
杰克 你的老婆 你认识的每个人都会陷入危险之中
Jack, your wife, everybody you know, they're in danger.
快滚
Now!
真是不错的谈话
Good talk.
杰克 我不知道你去了哪里 但你吓到我了
Jack, i don't know where you are, but you're scaring me.
回家吧 我们谈谈
Come home. we need to talk.
好吗
Please?
该死 杰克 不要
Damn it, jack, no!
跟上
Come on.
等等
Aah! wait!
我们是来救你的
Uh, we're here to save you, I guess.
我们该走了 是的
We should go. yeah.
米歇尔 我回来了
Michelle, i'm home.
宝贝
Hey, babe?
你在吗
Are you here?
米歇尔
Michelle.
米歇尔？
Michelle?
好吧 我们都保持冷静
Okay. we're gonna stay calm.
这个男的要什么我们都给他
We're gonna give this man whatever he wants.
任何东西 拿了就走 拜托
Anything. just take it and go, please.
我很抱歉 杰克
I'm sorry about this, jack.
真的抱歉
I truly am.
我并不想对你这样
It's not the way that I wanted it to go.
你是谁
Who are you?
你已经见过我朋友了
You already met some friends of mine.
两兄弟
Two brothers?
他们说如果我 听着 我谁也没伤害
They said that if I, look, I haven't hurt anybody.
还没有 但你会的
Not yet, but you would've.
他们总这样
They always do.
我来帮你个忙 孩子
I'm doing you a favor, son.
杰克 他说什么呢
Jack, what's he talking about?
告诉她吧 杰克
Tell her, jack.
告诉她真相 她有权知道
Tell her the truth. she deserves to know.
就让她走吧 她和此事无关
Just let her go. she's not a part of this.
和什么无关
A part of what?
杰克
Jack?!
我真的很抱歉 但她和这事有关系
I really do apologize, but she is part of it.
什么
What?
米歇尔
Michelle…
告诉他我到这以后你跟我说了什么
…tell him what you told me when I got here.
米歇尔
Michelle?
我说了
I said…
不要伤害我
"don't hurt me…
因为我怀孕了
Because I'm pregnant."
等一下
J-just hold on a minute.
你知道我们这儿多糟糕了吧
Now you see the mess we're in?
我不能再犯这个错误
I can't make this mistake all over again.
我30年内不会重复这个错误了 该了结了
I won't be around in 30 years. this has got to end now.
我知道你不信我 如果我可以不做这个你让我干嘛都行
I know you don't believe me, but I'd give anything not to have to do this.
别这样
No. no.
别
神啊 别这样
Oh, god. please don't!
你可以不这么做的
You don't have to do this!
如果你要杀我 动手吧 但别伤害我老婆
If you want to kill me, kill me, but not my wife.
好吗 求你了
Okay? I'm begging you.
没有机会了
Ain't got no choice.
同情你一下
My condolences.
杰克
Jack.
Jack!
离我远点
Stay away from me!
米歇尔
Michelle.
我猜我们现在可以找到特拉维斯了
I guess now we know where travis is.
这个傻蛋
That stupid son of a bitch.
我的神啊
Oh, god.
那个是特拉维斯
Think that's travis?
什么玩意把他丢在这里
What's left of him.
你对杰克的判断是正确的
Guess you were right about jack.
迪恩
Dean!
Dean?
迪恩现在不能接电话
Dean can't come to the phone right now.
杰克 如果你要敢伤害他 我向上帝发誓
Jack! if you hurt him, I swear to god!
冷静点
Calm down!
你兄弟死不了
Your brother's alive.
除非你冷静下来
But not if you don't calm down!
好吧 杰克 听着
All right, jack. listen.
开门 我们来解决问题 行么
Open the door. we can figure this out, okay?
我们需要动动脑筋现在
We'll have ourselves a little brainstorming session.
杰克 拜托了
Jack, please.
我不这么认为 你都做了什么
I don't think so. after what you did?
什么 说什么呢你
What? what are you talking about?
你把你朋友送来
You sent your friend here.
他想把我老婆活活烧死
He tried to burn my wife alive!
什么 为什么啊
What? why?
他没说
He didn't say.
我猜变态狂都不用解释原因
I guess psychopaths don't have to explain themselves.
听我说 你得相信我
Listen to me. you got to believe me.
我和我哥哥 我们绝对不会伤害她 好吗
My brother and i, we never would have hurt her, okay?
神啊 我饿死了
Oh, god, i'm so hungry.
杰克 别这么做
Jack, don't do this.
我再也没有家了
I can't ever see my family again.
你们俩 你朋友 你把我卷进来的
You two…your friend, you made me into this!
没人让你杀我们
No one's making you kill us.
听我说
Listen to me.
我知道你体内有无法控制的力量
You got this dark pit inside you. I know.
相信我 我理解
Believe me, i know.
但这不代表你不可救药了
But that doesn't mean you have to fall into it.
你不用成为一个怪物
You don't have to be a monster.
你后来看到过我没有
Have you seen me lately?
你是什么不重要 重要的是你做什么
It doesn't matter what you are. it only matters what you do.
自己选择吧
It's your choice.
杰克
Jack!
你做的对 你知道吧
You did the right thing, you know.
这家伙是个怪物 他不会变的
That guy was a monster. there was no going back.
萨姆 我想跟你道歉
Sam, i want to tell you I'm sorry.
我有段时间对你太苛刻
I've been kind of hard on you lately.
别多想了 迪恩
Don't worry about it, Dean.
只是你
It's just that your,
你的预感 让我害怕了
Uh, your psychic thing, it scares the crap out of me.
如果这都是一样的 我再也不会说这些了
If it's all the same, i'd really rather not talk about it.
等等 什么 你不想说了 你
Wait a minute. what? you don't want to talk? you?
没什么好说的
There's nothing more to say.
我说不清楚跟你
I can't keep explaining myself to you.
你没法理解
I can't make you understand.
你为什么不试试 我不能
Why don't you try? I can't.
因为这玩意 这他妈 这不是在你身上 是在我身上
Because th thing, this blood, it's not in you the way it's in me.
我得亲自处理这玩意
It's just something I got to deal with.
我奉陪
Not alone.
反正无所谓了
Anyway, it doesn't matter.
这些邪灵 他们操纵烈焰
These powers, it's playing with fire.
我搞定它们了
I'm done with them.
我搞定所有事情了
I'm done with everything.
真的
Really?
那真不错
Well, that's a relief.
多谢
Thank you.
别谢我 我又不是为你做的
Don't thank me. I'm not doing it for you.
或是给天使或其他什么人
Or for the angels or for anybody.
这是我自己的选择
This is my choice.